Pelham, Ruth; Papers apap408
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Albany Housing Authority (AHA), 1986-2002; 3; 1.43 cubic ft.
  - "If I Could Wish" Song Sheets, Attendance Sheets, Promotional Materials, and Financial Information, 1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Permission Forms for Music Mobile's Video - RESTRICTED, 1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Various Notes, Letters, Attendance Sheets, 1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - "We Talked it Out" Songbook - Corning Homes, 1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - "When I Do My Part" Project - Corning Homes, 1997; Undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Beat of the Street' Documentary Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - AHA Contract 2000 and Promotional Materials, 1998-2000; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1999 "Music In My Neighborhood" Survey Forms (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AHA Contract, Attendance Sheets, and Programming - RESTRICTED, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Music in My Neighborhood" 99 Kid's Survey, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Music in My Neighborhood" 99 Parent Survey, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 2000 AHA Program Attendance Information, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Music Mobile PHDEP Voucher and Activity Report and AHA Spring 2000 Afterschool Flyers - RESTRICTED, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Spring AHA Programs (Mainly Tobacco Free Youth Programming), 2000-2001; Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "The Public Speaker", 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - AHA Attendance Sheets - "Music In My Neighborhood", Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Attendance Sheets and Posters for "If I Could Wish" Family Concert Series, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Flyer for "If I Could Wish" Family Concert at Ezra Prentice Boys and Girls Club, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - "If I Could Wish" J-Card, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "If I Could Wish" Lyrics - Ida Yarbrough Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - "If I Could Wish" Songbook - Ida Yarbrough Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - "If I Could Wish" Song Sheets, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Illustrations and Song Lyrics Work - Corning Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - "It's My Community" Lyrics - Ida Yarbrough Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "It's My Community" Project - Ida Yarbrough Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "It's My Community" Songbook - Ida Yarbrough Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Recording Information for "If I Could Wish" Project, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ruth's Drawings, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Song Ideas from Corning Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Song Ideas from Corning Homes, Undated (Flat-file 3)
  - Song Lyrics and Group Worksheets from Ezra Prentice Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Song Lyrics Groupwork Sheet - Ezra Prentice Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Song Lyrics Worksheets - Ida Yarbrough Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Song Sheets, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Songwriting/Family Concert Flyers 95, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Songwriting Project Costs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - "This Is our Neighborhood" Song Sheets, Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - "Up The Hill" Project - Ida Yarbrough Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - "Up The Hill" Songbook - Corning Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - "Up The Hill" Songbook - Ida Yarbrough Homes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Words to Housing Authority Songs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)